cocoafab.com 2018-03-18

# Privacy Policy | Cocoa Media Group, LLC | CocoaFab

**Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting CocoaFab.com, a site wholly owned and operated by Cocoa Media Group, LLC. Because your privacy is very important to us we have provided this privacy statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on our Site(s).

**The Information We Collect**

We, our service providers, advertisers and partners may collect personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information when you visit any of our Site(s).

When registering for an account on our Site(s), we may require you to provide us with contact information, such a name, address, phone number and e-mail address and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services.Â  We also collect personally identifiable information when you participate in any contest, sweepstakes, survey or other promotion.

A representative list of the types of non-personally identifiable information we may collect include, but is not limited to: current Internet protocol address and type of browser you are using (e.g., Google, Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast, Verizon or AT&T), the web pages you have visited, sites visited before and after you visit our Site(s), the type of handheld or mobile device used to view the site (e.g., iPhone, Blackberry), location information, the content you have accessed and the advertisements you have been shown and/or clicked on.

You can also engage with our content and other offerings, on or through third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook and Twitter, and third-party social media plug-ins and applications. When you engage with our content on or through third party social networking sites, plug-ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the â€˜likes’ you make) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application. We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., content viewed, information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on,) from your interaction with our content.

When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our applications or websites, and (3) contact you through the social networking sites or directly by sending you the latest news and special offerings. By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with our privacy policy. When you provide personal information to us through an application, on our Site(s), or on social networking sites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties.

Through some social networking sites’ privacy settings, you can control what data you share. For more information about how social networking sites handle your personal information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use.

**How We Use the Information**

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, to enforce the legal terms that govern your use of our Site(s), and/or for the purposes for which you provided the information.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or to share new information.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products or services.

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a letter to our editors, comments, a posting to a blog or a discussion board, a video), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us.

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Site(s), to deliver more relevant marketing messages and advertisements and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information to analyze usage of our Site(s), as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Site(s) and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. In addition, we may transfer personally identifiable information about you if we, or one of our business units, are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another entity.

We may share personally identifiable information with agents and contractors of Cocoa Media Group so that these agents and contracts to enable them to provide services and to ensure the quality of information provided.Â  Our agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy statement and are not authorized to use the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy statement.

We may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties whose practices are not covered by this privacy statement (e.g., other marketers, web sites, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. If a Cocoa Media Group Â site shares personally identifiable information, the site will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses either at the point of submission of your personally identifiable information or prior to any such disclosure.

If you have signed up to receive our e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from our Site(s). To provide visitors with additional or more relevant product and service opportunities, we may share non-personally identifiable information with third parties.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

To enhance your online experience, we use “cookies” or similar technologies. Cookies do not contain personally identifiable information; however, once you choose to furnish a site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site and Internet usage and to improve or customize the content, offerings or advertisements on our Site(s).

We, our third party service providers, advertisers or our partners also may use cookies to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through Cocoa Media Group Site(s) and/or other sites. This also helps us, our service providers and partners provide more relevant advertising.Â  This privacy statement does not cover the use of third party cookies.

We, our third party service providers, advertiser or our partners may also use “web beacons” or clear .gifs, or similar technologies, which are small pieces of code placed on a web page, to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page including standard information from your web browser such as browser type, your internet protocol (IP) address, web pages viewed and links to other websites clicked. For example, web beacons may be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page.

You can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies will affect your online experience and may prevent you from enjoying the full features offered on our Site(s).

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad Servers, and Sponsors**

Some of our Site(s) contain links to or integrations with other sites such as Facebook, Twitter, etc., whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Cocoa Media Group Site(s) covered by this privacy statement may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, promotions, games, applications, or social network integrations) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. We have no control over these third parties’ use of this information. The site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

We also use the services of reputable third parties to provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and site analytics, as well as to assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit or set their own cookies. We, our third party service providers, advertisers and/or partners may also place web beacons for these third parties. Cocoa Media Group is not responsible for the information practices or content of third party sites.Â  The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this privacy statement.Â  We encourage you to review the privacy statements of such third party sites to understand their information practices.

**Ad Choices**

Our goal is to provide you with ads that are relevant to you. Â Where possible our ads are based on the content of pages you are viewing, but we also try to provide ads tailored to your interests.

As discussed in the section titled Cookies and Web Beacons, some information is collected about you automatically through cookies and web beacons.

You can change your browser settings to reject all cookies, accept only certain cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Â Please note that you may need to renew these settings if you delete your cookies after these preferences are made. Â These settings also may not apply if you are using a different computer or Internet browser. If you use other computers or browsers and want to adjust your cookies settings for interest-based ads on any of those sites, you will need to repeat this process for each computer or browser.

Many third-party advertising networks are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). To opt out of having information collected by NAI member companies used for behavioral advertising, to obtain information about the technologies these ad networks might use, and to view information regarding their privacy policies, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp.

If you opt out of these technologies, you will continue to see advertising displayed on our Site(s), but the advertising may not be targeted to your interests.

**Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and to use correctly the information we collect online.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this site you may contact us at [privacypolicy@cocoamediagroup.com](mailto:privacypolicy@CocoaMediaGroup.com).

**Updates & Effective Date**

From time to time, we may update this privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this statement so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it.

The Privacy Statement posted on this site was updated September 2012.

﻿
